Finding Aid for the Donald Kalish Papers LSC.0578
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Los Angeles magazine, 1969 November (Box 179, Folder 9)
- David Kaplan's press release, 1969 September (Box 179, Folder 10)
- Articles and clippings on Angela Davis, 1971-1972 (Box 179, Folder 11)
- UCSB El Gaucho articles on Angela Davis, 1969 November 4 (Box 179, Folder 12)
- "The Constitutional Rights of Communist Teachers and the Angela Davis Case," John Somerville, 1972 (Box 179, Folder 13)
- San Francisco Chronicle on Angela Davis, 1969 October 21 (Box 179, Folder 14-17)
- San Francisco Examiner and Chronicle on Angela Davis, 1969 September 21 (Box 179, Folder 18)
- Los Angeles Times article Angela Davis, 1975-1977 (Box 179, Folder 19)
- Angela Davis materials, undated (Box 179, Folder 20)
- Newspaper clippings on Angela Davis case, 1969 (Box 179, Folder 21)
- UCLA Alumni magazine (Fall), 1969 (Box 179, Folder 22)
- Time magazine, 1969 October 17 (Box 180, Folder 1)
- I.F. Stone nomination, 1971-1982 (Box 180, Folder 2)
- Letters of recommendation, 1976-1977 (Box 180, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 133: Recommendations, 1975-1976 (Box 180, Folder 4)
- Letters of recommendation, 1974 (Box 180, Folder 5)
- Edward Glassberg undergrad award, 1978 January (Box 180, Folder 6)
- Kalbus, Kurt, Zierman, and Scott, 1978 (Box 180, Folder 7)
- Gordon Kido, 1975-1978 (Box 180, Folder 8)
- Debbie Cooper, 1974-1980 (Box 180, Folder 9)
- Joel Elkins, 1984 March (Box 180, Folder 10)
- Jay Cone, 1983 (Box 180, Folder 11)
- Fariborz Ehsani, 1983 (Box 180, Folder 12)
- Donald Freed, 1983 (Box 180, Folder 13)
- Janine Gershon, 1976-1983 (Box 180, Folder 14)
- Philosophy 133: Recommendations, 1976-1977 (Box 180, Folder 15)
- David Dolinko, 1976 December 15 (Box 180, Folder 16)
- Cheryl Bascom thank you note, and Freed, 1976-1977 (Box 180, Folder 17)
- Hugh Gibbons, 1977 (Box 180, Folder 18)
- Janice Leyrer, 1974-1980 (Box 180, Folder 19)
- Palle Yourgrau (Fall), 1978 (Box 180, Folder 20)
- Joseph Owens, 1979 (Box 180, Folder 21)
- Leslie Kay Whiteside, 1979 (Box 180, Folder 22)
- Rebecca Kurth Rhodes scholarship, 1979 (Box 180, Folder 23)
- James Morris, undated (Box 180, Folder 24)
- Steven Green, 1980 (Box 180, Folder 25)
- Fumiaka Matusoka, 1980 (Box 180, Folder 26)
- David Vriend, 1978-1983 (Box 180, Folder 27)
- Tom Hill, 1981 (Box 180, Folder 28)
- Notes on Dana Scott, undated (Box 180, Folder 29)
- "An Independence of Axiom of Choice" Dana, undated (Box 180, Folder 30)
- Montague's set theory course notes (Fall), 1964 (Box 180, Folder 31)
- Philosophy 184A: Final exams (Spring), 1963 (Box 180, Folder 32)
- Master sheets for ditto notes, undated (Box 181, Folder 1)
- Mostowski on finite sets and Lambert translation, 1938 (Box 181, Folder 2)
- Set theory notes by Dana Scott (Fall), 1964 (Box 181, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 184A: Theorem list (Fall), 1963 (Box 181, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 184A: Exams (Fall), 1963 (Box 181, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 184A: Final exam (Spring), 1963 (Box 181, Folder 6)
- Set theory course and theorem list (Spring), 1963 (Box 181, Folder 7)
- Los Angeles Times clippings on Angela Davis (Fall), 1969 (Box 181, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 31: Sentential and quantifier logic, identity, and descriptions (Fall), 1955 (Box 181, Folder 9)
- Philosophy 31: Cooley, 1949-1951 (Box 181, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 31: Lecture, syllabus, and exam, Cooley, 1952-1954 (Box 181, Folder 11)
- Philsophy 184: Theory of identity, some theorems (Spring), 1954 (Box 181, Folder 12)
- Philosophy 184: Deduction, inductive step in proof (Spring), 1954 (Box 181, Folder 13)
- A natural deduction system for sentential calculus, undated (Box 181, Folder 14)
- Quine: "Glimpses Beyond Problems in Higher Order Calculi", 1948-1953 (Box 181, Folder 15)
- Spatial learning and No. 5 proofs, undated (Box 181, Folder 16)
- Philosophy 30: Inductive logic lecture notes, 1950-1951 (Box 182, Folder 1)
- The Uninterpreted System SC, undated (Box 182, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 184: Sentential calculus syllabus (Spring), 1954 (Box 182, Folder 3)
- Notes and paper on Charles S. Peirce, 1944 (Box 182, Folder 4)
- Ethics (Fall), 1939 (Box 182, Folder 5)
- Aesthetics, undated (Box 182, Folder 6)
- "History of Art", 1939 (Box 182, Folder 7)
- "The Philosophy of the 19th Century" with Mackay while undergraduate, undated (Box 182, Folder 8)
- Notes and paper on pragmatism, 1938 (Box 183, Folder 1)
- Stanford course "Intellectual History of the US" (Spring), 1942 (Box 183, Folder 2)
- Papers and notes on "A Study of History by Toynbee", 1940 (Box 183, Folder 3)
- Vocabulary and its application as an air cadet, 1934 (Box 183, Folder 4)
- War morale (Stanford), 1941 (Box 183, Folder 5)
- Naturalism, 1949-1950 (Box 183, Folder 6)
- Ruth Yearous' Blue Book 6B at Berk, undated (Box 183, Folder 7)
- Notes in connection with thesis, undated (Box 183, Folder 8)
- "Der Wahrheitsbegriff" translation, undated (Box 183, Folder 9)
- Freshman courses in astronomy, physics, and chemistry, 1940 (Box 183, Folder 10)
- French translations, 1938 (Box 183, Folder 11)
- Notes on mathematics, 1944 (Box 184, Folder 1)
- German grammar, undated (Box 184, Folder 2)
- Paper on semantics in "The Categories of Naturalism" by Will Dennes, undated (Box 184, Folder 3)
- "The Criterion of Significance," Marhenke, 1950 (Box 184, Folder 4)
- Rough draft of "Meaning as Entities", 1952 (Box 184, Folder 5)
- Semantics notes (Fall), 1951 (Box 184, Folder 6)
- Semantics seminar (Spring), 1953 (Box 184, Folder 7)
- Goodman on synonymity, 1952 August 13 (Box 184, Folder 8)
- Notes and paper on "Freedom of the Will", undated (Box 184, Folder 9)
- Partial manuscript of Morris's "Signs, Language, and Behavior" with comments, undated (Box 184, Folder 10)
- Notes on a "Behavioristic Approach to Meaning," Morris, Tolman, and Gomprez, 1943 (Box 184, Folder 11)
- "Der Wahrheitsbegriff in den formalisierten Sprachen", undated (Box 184, Folder 12)
- Logical truths, 1952 (Box 184, Folder 13)
- First draft of explication of "is true", 1952 (Box 184, Folder 14)
- "Synonymity" rough draft, 1952 (Box 184, Folder 15)
- "On Significance," D. Kaplan, 1959 January (Box 184, Folder 16)
- "The Nomenclature of Information Theory" by D.M. MacKay, 1950-1951 (Box 184, Folder 17)
- "The Theory of Descriptions, Part I", 1952 July (Box 185, Folder 1)
- Logical form, undated (Box 185, Folder 2)
- Logical form article from thesis by Kalish, undated (Box 185, Folder 3)
- German translations, 1935-1949 (Box 185, Folder 4)
- Notes on Pap's "Existence, Logic, and the Theory of Descriptions", 1953 September (Box 185, Folder 5)
- People's Coalition for Peace and Justice, 1971 (Box 185, Folder 6)
- American Friends Service Committee, 1971 May 27 (Box 185, Folder 7)
- Bradford Lyttle Defense Committee, 1971 (Box 185, Folder 8)
- Spring movement newspaper clippings (Spring), 1971 (Box 185, Folder 9)
- People's Peace Treaty, 1971 (Box 185, Folder 10)
- Newspaper clippings on Vietnam, 1967 (Box 185, Folder 11)
- Resist newsletter, 1969 (Box 186, Folder 1)
- Resist newsletter, 1968 (Box 186, Folder 2)
- Resist newsletter, 1970 (Box 186, Folder 3)
- "The Conspiracy" newspaper clippings, 1970 (Box 186, Folder 4)
- Newspaper clippings on campus actions and war, 1970 (Box 186, Folder 5)
- Arms race, 1983 (Box 187, Folder 1)
- Newspaper clippings on Central America, 1983 (Box 187, Folder 2)
- Middle East, 1983 (Box 187, Folder 3)
- Concerned Faculty materials, 1983 (Box 187, Folder 4)
- Newspaper clippings on rape prevention program, 1983 (Box 187, Folder 5)
- Concerned Faculty: Records of contributions and printed stationery, 1982 (Box 187, Folder 6)
- Lebanon petition and correspondence, 1982 (Box 187, Folder 7-8)
- Concerned Faculty signatures, 1982 (Box 187, Folder 9)
- Newspaper clippings on Lebanon, 1982 (Box 187, Folder 10)
- UCAM/Union of Concerned Scientists, 1982 (Box 187, Folder 11)
- Concerned Faculty on nuclear weapons freeze, 1982 October (Box 187, Folder 12)
- Newspaper clippings on nuclear arms race, 1981-1982 (Box 187, Folder 13)
- Project for global education, 1982 (Box 188, Folder 1)
- Newspaper clippings on Saxon's conference, 1982 (Box 188, Folder 2)
- Concerned Faculty correspondence with participants, 1981-1982 (Box 188, Folder 3)
- Correspondence with Willens, 1981-1982 (Box 188, Folder 4)
- Saxon's budget requests, 1982-1983 (Box 188, Folder 5)
- Johnson report, 1982 (Box 188, Folder 6)
- Center for International and Strategic Affairs, 1981-1982 (Box 188, Folder 7)
- George Brown correspondence, 1969-1983 (Box 188, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1969-1983 (Box 188, Folder 9, Box 189, Folder 1)
- Framed sketch, undated (Box 189, Folder 2)
- Foreign Policy clippings on Institute of International Studies, 1983 (Box 189, Folder 3)
- SEARCH (Palestine), undated (Box 189, Folder 4)
- UC and Angela Davis, 1968-1970 (Box 189, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 184B: Predicate calculus (Spring), 1960 (Box 190, Folder 1)
- Purely sentential systems (Spring), 1963 (Box 190, Folder 2)
- Notes on functional completeness, 1958 (Box 190, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 184B: Decision procedures (Spring), 1963 (Box 190, Folder 4)
- Predicate calculus, 1958 (Box 190, Folder 5)
- "Traditional Logic and Modern Logic" by Thomas F. Mosimann for Oxford, 1965 August (Box 190, Folder 6)
- First lectures on sentential logic (Spring), 1974 (Box 190, Folder 7)
- Lecture Three: The chaste first order functional calculus, undated (Box 190, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 184B: Completeness of Sentential calculus (Spring), 1963 (Box 190, Folder 9)
- Philosophy proof specification from weak specification, 1972 September (Box 190, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 135: Extra handouts (Spring), 1972 (Box 190, Folder 11)
- Transforms, theorem proof, 1972 September (Box 190, Folder 12)
- Philosophy 135: Extra handouts (Fall), 1972 (Box 190, Folder 13)
- Philosophy 135: Other materials (Fall), 1972 (Box 190, Folder 14)
- Philosophy 135: Lou Narens and class notes (Winter), 1972 (Box 190, Folder 15)
- Boolean valued models for higher order logic, Dana Scott, 1966 April (Box 190, Folder 16)
- Philosophy 135: Class notes (Fall), 1972 (Box 190, Folder 17)
- Compactness theorem, sequential logic, and Quine's proof, 1972 (Box 190, Folder 18)
- Articles on nonstandard analysis and Robinson, 1972 June (Box 190, Folder 19)
- "Truth and Proof" by Alfred Tarski in Scientific American, 1969 June (Box 190, Folder 20)
- Hermes proof for Quine's system, 184B notes, and other materials (Spring), 1960 (Box 190, Folder 21)
- Loose mimeograph papers, undated (Box 190, Folder 22)
- Philosophy 187B: Revised notes, Graef, undated (Box 190, Folder 23)
- Church's review of Martin-Greach on material criterion, undated (Box 190, Folder 24)
- Philosophy 187B: Notes on truth, I-truth, and analyticity, 1953, 1964 (Box 191, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 187B: Material on modal logic (Spring), 1959 (Box 191, Folder 2-3)
- Philosophy 187B: Final exam (Spring), 1964 (Box 191, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 187B: Kalish notes on theorems (Spring), 1964 (Box 191, Folder 5)
- Church semantics, notes by Sam Soderstrum, 1960-1961 (Box 191, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 187B: Other materials, undated (Box 191, Folder 7-9)
- Semantics materials, undated (Box 191, Folder 10)
- Modal sentential logic (S52) by natural deduction (Merrill), 1975 (Box 191, Folder 11)
- Kaplan's modal logic (Fall), 1975 (Box 191, Folder 12)
- References for semantics, 1959-1960 (Box 191, Folder 13)
- Philosophy 182: Logic and meaning, exams, bluebooks, 1960 October (Box 191, Folder 14)
- Philosophy 184B: Stencils and homework assignments (Fall), 1956 (Box 191, Folder 15)
- Set theory rough notes, undated (Box 191, Folder 16)
- Philosophy 184B: Bibliographical material, undated (Box 191, Folder 17)
- Philosophy 184B: Rough notes, undated (Box 191, Folder 18)
- Political pamphlets: "Law in Transition", 1964 (Box 192, Folder 1)
- University reviews, 1956, 1969-1970 (Box 192, Folder 2)
- "The Ideological Function of the University" pamphlet by Richard Lichtman, 1967 December 24 (Box 192, Folder 3)
- Extracts from Arab school texts, 1967-1968 (Box 192, Folder 4)
- Political cartoons pamphlet, 1968 August 22 (Box 192, Folder 5)
- Vietnam pamphlets, 1969-1970 (Box 192, Folder 6)
- Logic 113: Propositional calculus, undated (Box 192, Folder 7)
- Philosophy 14 and Philosophy 124 notes, undated (Box 192, Folder 8)
- Exams, 1934-1937 (Box 192, Folder 9-10)
- Logic 113: Predicate calculus with identity and descriptions, undated (Box 193, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1971 January (Box 193, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1971 February (Box 193, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1971 March (Box 193, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1971 April-July (Box 193, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1971 August-October (Box 193, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1971 November-December (Box 193, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1972 January-March (Box 193, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1971 April-June (Box 193, Folder 9)
- Lawyers Guild correspondence and news clippings, 1971-1973 (Box 193, Folder 10)
- People's Party correspondence (Spock et al), 1971 December 22 (Box 193, Folder 11)
- National Students Association pamphlets and newsletters, 1969-1970 (Box 193, Folder 12)
- United States Servicemen's Fund and Support Our Soldiers letters and pamphlets, 1972 (Box 193, Folder 13)
- Sacharoff on conduct of Indochina War, 1970-1972 (Box 193, Folder 14)
- American Civil Liberties Union and National Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 193, Folder 15)
- Southern Conference Educational Fund, 1970-1973 (Box 193, Folder 16)
- War Resister League, WIN Magazine, and correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 193, Folder 17)
- American Friends Service Committee correspondence and newsletters, 1971-1972 (Box 194, Folder 1)
- American Friends Service Committee materials on draft, 1971 (Box 194, Folder 2)
- Fellowship of Reconciliation newsletter, 1969-1971 (Box 194, Folder 3)
- National Committee Against Repressive Legislation, 1971-1973 (Box 194, Folder 4)
- Clergy and laymen concerned about Vietnam, 1970-1972 (Box 194, Folder 5)
- University Council and American Federation of Teachers, 1969-1972 (Box 194, Folder 6)
- Correspondence on various political causes, 1971 (Box 194, Folder 7)
- New American Movement and registered organizations at UCLA, 1971 February (Box 194, Folder 8)
- The Resistance: Berkeley, San Francisco, and Palo Alto offices, 1968 (Box 195, Folder 1)
- The Resistance: Los Angeles office, 1968-1969 (Box 195, Folder 2)
- The Resistance: Bronxton office, 1967-1968 (Box 195, Folder 3)
- The Resistance: New England and Philadelphia offices, 1968-1969 (Box 195, Folder 4)
- The Resistance: Bruce Dancis, 1967 (Box 195, Folder 5)
- SC Supporters of the Resistance and opposing the draft, undated (Box 195, Folder 6)
- Signatures and contributions advert, 1967 (Box 195, Folder 7)
- United Resistance Fund, undated (Box 195, Folder 8)
- Iranian Students Association, 1971-1972 (Box 195, Folder 9)
- Manual for Republican Convention, 1972 (Box 195, Folder 10)
- Glen Baron, Bruce Baron, Walt Chun, Jim Maffie, and Terry Colvin group project, 1971 March (Box 196, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 150B: Charles Parret, Joseph Sawyer, Gary Soter, and Kaye Tucker student projects, 1971 March (Box 196, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 150B: Don Crowell, Charles Darby, Maxene Spellman, and Ray Gordezky student projects, 1971 March (Box 196, Folder 3)
- Paul Schmidt, Stan Gryde, Peter Heman, and Micheline Herskovic student projects, 1971 March (Box 196, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 150B: Strick, Tobin, Troncoso, and Van Pelt student projects (Winter), 1971 (Box 196, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 150B: Reinstein, Rouse, Rosso, and Sauer student projects, 1971 (Box 196, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 150B: Exams (Winter), 1971 (Box 196, Folder 7)
- Philosophy 150B: Towry, Adams, Brown, and Halliburton student projects (Winter), 1971 (Box 196, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 150B: Stewart, Jacobs, Walsh, and Lau student projects, 1971 (Box 196, Folder 9)
- Philosophy 150B: Soo, Schwarzbach, and Manning student projects (Winter), 1971 (Box 196, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 150B: Eberhardt, Fein, Humpal, and Logan student projects, 1971 (Box 196, Folder 11)
- Huey Newton's birthday poster, undated (Box 197, Folder 1)
- "Killed in Vietnam" poster, undated (Box 197, Folder 2)
- "Bring Them Home Alive" poster, undated (Box 197, Folder 3)
- "Rich Man's War" poster, undated (Box 197, Folder 4)
- Charles Bragg poster, undated (Box 197, Folder 5)
- "Stop the War/Stop Nixon" poster, undated (Box 197, Folder 6)
- "Those Who Have/Had A Chance" poster, undated (Box 197, Folder 7)
- "May Day" poster, undated (Box 197, Folder 8)
- "New Paper Broadsides" posters, undated (Box 197, Folder 9)
- Women Strike for Peace newsletters, 1980-1983 (Box 198, Folder 1)
- George Brown, Anthony Beilenson, and Alan Cranston, 1979-1981 (Box 198, Folder 2)
- War Resisters League and David McReynolds correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 198, Folder 3)
- Newspaper clippings, 1980-1981 (Box 198, Folder 4)
- Committee to Bridge the Gap, 1980-1981 (Box 198, Folder 5)
- Mobilization for Survival newsletters, 1982-1983 (Box 198, Folder 6)
- Handgun control newsletters and correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 198, Folder 7)
- National Organization for Women materials, undated (Box 198, Folder 8)
- Resist newsletter and correspondence, 1972-1983 (Box 199, Folder 1-2)
- Promoting Enduring Peace movement literature, 1980 (Box 199, Folder 3)
- Asian Center correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 199, Folder 4)
- National Committee Against Repressive Legislation correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 199, Folder 5)
- Institute for Policy Studies newsletters, 1980-1981 (Box 199, Folder 6)
- Correspondence on El Salvador, 1981-1982 (Box 199, Folder 7)
- U.S. Committee Against Nuclear War, 1983 February 11 (Box 199, Folder 8)
- Physicians for Social Responsibility correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 199, Folder 9)
- Court materials: Case 2Civ. No. 35485, 1969 (Box 200, Folder 1-2)
- "Who's in Charge here?" by Harold Keen in newsletter, undated (Box 200, Folder 3)
- Newspaper clippings and newsletters on Asia and Vietnam, 1973 (Box 200, Folder 4)
- Set the Date adverts in newspapers, 1972 (Box 200, Folder 5)
- Set the Date agenda steering committee, 1972 April (Box 200, Folder 6)
- Air War Initiative, undated (Box 200, Folder 7)
- Posters of adverts appearing in newspapers, 1972 (Box 200, Folder 8)
- Set the Date campaign contributions, 1972 (Box 201, Folder 1-2)
- Event pins for women's rights campaigns, 1964-1984 (Box 201, Folder 3)
- Set the Date sponsors correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 201, Folder 4)
- Contacts: Help in CD's and office, 1971 (Box 201, Folder 5)
- Contacts: DCT notes (Set the Date), 1972 (Box 201, Folder 6)
- Congressional votes and military operations correspondence and clippings, 1972 (Box 201, Folder 7)
- Steering Committee report, 1972 (Box 201, Folder 8)
- Ad cover letters, Kalish and Willens, 1971 (Box 201, Folder 9)
- "Commit Rabbi Lewis" advert and correspondence, 1972 February (Box 202, Folder 1)
- "Out of Asia or Out of Office" advert in newspaper, 1971 (Box 202, Folder 2)
- Set the Date: Inter-religious campaign to end the war, 1972 (Box 202, Folder 3)
- Set the Date: Student correspondence, 1972 (Box 202, Folder 4)
- Data on CDs, undated (Box 202, Folder 5)
- Congressmen's reaction to advert, 1972 (Box 202, Folder 6)
- College contacts and notes, undated (Box 202, Folder 7)
- Congressmen's response to telegrams, 1972 (Box 202, Folder 8)
- Set the Date correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 202, Folder 9)
- New York Times advert and contacts, 1971-1972 (Box 202, Folder 10)
- Anti-war bill, Gravel, Mondale, Drinan, 1972 March (Box 202, Folder 11)
- Anti-war adverts and Set the Date events, 1971-1972 (Box 202, Folder 12)
- California Federation of Teachers-Conference on Women in Higher Education, 1973 (Box 202, Folder 13)
- CD zip codes, 1971 (Box 202, Folder 14)
- May 4th Moratorium Day notes, clippings, and correspondence, 1972 (Box 202, Folder 15)
- Set the Date advert and senators' votes, 1971 (Box 202, Folder 16)
- Set the Date campaign contributions correspondence, 1972 (Box 202, Folder 17)
- Leo Baeck Temple, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 1)
- Set the Date progress, 1972 February (Box 203, Folder 2)
- Steering Committee CD contacts, undated (Box 203, Folder 3)
- News releases, 1971-1972 (Box 203, Folder 4)
- Newspaper advert clippings and correspondence, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 5)
- Set the Date: KNXT education and Nixon's speech, 1972 (Box 203, Folder 6)
- Set the Date: Radio spots on PSB, 1972 (Box 203, Folder 7)
- Set the Date meeting at Westwood United Methodist Church, 1972 February 16 (Box 203, Folder 8)
- News release on Nixon's speech, 1972 (Box 203, Folder 9)
- Set the Date after April 1, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 10)
- Set the Date: Poll, undated (Box 203, Folder 11)
- Revised petitions and cover letter, 1971-1972 (Box 203, Folder 12)
- Veteran and GI corresondence, undated (Box 203, Folder 13)
- Set the Date: Record of rally ticket sales, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 14)
- Brochures and newsletters, 1972 (Box 203, Folder 15)
- Text of the Boland amendment, 1971 November (Box 203, Folder 16)
- Set the Date: Ellsberg Ralley publicity statement, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 17)
- Valley Peace Center Vietnam fact sheet, undated (Box 203, Folder 18)
- Vietnam War fact sheet, undated (Box 203, Folder 19)
- News clippings, 1971-1972 (Box 203, Folder 20)
- Newspaper clippings on social issue, 1972 (Box 203, Folder 21)
- Statement on Middle East, undated (Box 203, Folder 22)
- Set the Date: Resolutions and cities, undated (Box 203, Folder 23)
- Harold Willens speech at Businessmen for Peace Dinner at Beverly Hilton Hotel, 1971 December (Box 203, Folder 24)
- Friends Committee on Legislation and profiles of Congressmen, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 25)
- Set the Date: Congressional District activity news, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 26)
- Congressmen profiles: Burt Talcott (12th congressional district), 1971-1972 (Box 203, Folder 27)
- Congressmen profiles: Charles Teagu (13th congressional district), 1971-1972 (Box 203, Folder 28)
- Congressmen profiles: B.F. Sisk (16th congressional district), 1971 (Box 203, Folder 29)
- Congressmen profiles: R. Mathias (18th congressional district), 1971 (Box 203, Folder 30)
- Congressmen profiles: C. Holifield (19th congressional district), 1971-1972 (Box 204, Folder 1)
- Congressmen profiles: H.A. Smith (20th congressional district), 1971-1972 (Box 204, Folder 2)
- Congressmen profiles: A. Hawkins (21st congressional district), 1971 (Box 204, Folder 3)
- Congressmen profiles: James Corman (22nd congressional districts), 1971-1972 (Box 204, Folder 4)
- Congressmen profiles: Del Clawson (23rd congressional districts), 1971 (Box 204, Folder 5)
- Congressmen profiles: J. Rousselo (24th congressional district), 1971 (Box 204, Folder 6)
- Congressmen profiles: C. Wiggins (25th congressional district), 1971 (Box 204, Folder 7)
- Congressmen profiles: Thomas Rees (26th congressional district), 1971-1972 (Box 204, Folder 8)
- Congressmen profiles: B. Goldwater (27th congressional districts), 1971-1972 (Box 204, Folder 9)
- Congressmen profiles: Alfonso Bell (28th congressional districts), 1971-1972 (Box 204, Folder 10)
- Congressmen profiles: Edward Roybal (30th congressional district), 1971 (Box 204, Folder 11)
- Congressmen profiles: G. Danielson (29th congressional districts), 1971-1972 (Box 204, Folder 12)
- Congressmen profiles: C. Wilson (31st congressional districts), 1971-1972 (Box 204, Folder 13)
- Congressmen profiles: Craig Hosmer (32nd congressional district), 1971-1972 (Box 204, Folder 14)
- Congressmen profiles: J.L. Pettis (33rd congressional district), 1971-1972 (Box 204, Folder 15)
- Congressmen profiles: Richard Hanna (34th congressional district), 1971-1972 (Box 204, Folder 16)
- Congressmen profiles: Glen Anderson (17th congressional district), 1971-1972 (Box 204, Folder 17)
- Congressmen profiles: John Schmitz (35th congressional district), 1971 (Box 204, Folder 18)